Meron Molla

Junior Data Analyst | SQL Server

Diligent customer service and cashier boasts over five years of experience. Recently achieved an MSc in Computer Science and completed the Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate. Entry-level data analytics professional proficient in data wrangling, modeling, visualization, and reporting using SQL, Excel, Python, and BI tools. Strong communication, organizational, and analytical skills.

meronalebachew44@gmail.com

(919)-656-2736

North Carolina, United States

meronmolla.com/

linkedin.com/in/meronmolla

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Rater TransPerfec

08/2023 - Present

Georgia, US

Tasks

- Evaluate and rate data quality according to established guidelines, ensuring work quality.
- Utilize specialized tools and software to assess and categorize various types of data.
- Contribute insights and recommendations for process improvements to optimize data rating efficiency.

Customer service DeKalb Farmers Market

02/2017 - 09/2020

Georgia, US

Tasks

- Provided excellent customer service and achieved a high rate of client satisfaction and retention.
- Monitored, directed, and prioritized store front-end activities in a fast-paced environment.
- Answering calls and worked with my supervisor to address any outstanding issues or concerns.
- Processing and generating reports.

EDUCATION

MSc, Computer Science American College of Technology

2020 - 2022

Graduate with High Honors

Study Program

American College of Technology

Courses

- Data Warehouse and Data Mining
- Software Engineering
- Computer security and privacy
- Project Management

SKILLS



Teamwork, Multitasking, Adaptability, Research.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- MS Degree In Computer Science GPA 3.8
- SQL Server Certificate
- Google Data Analytic Certificate

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

Please click the link below

- https://meronmolla.com/
- https://github.com/MeronMolla

LANGUAGES

English
Full Professional Proficiency

Amharic

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Technology

Business

Art

Education